<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ImProvider Mikrotik</string>
    <string name="hyperlink"><a href="https://itremedy.online/">by ITRemedy</a></string>
    <string name="connect">CONNECT</string>
    <string name="password">Password :</string>
    <string name="username">Username :</string>
    <string name="port">Port :</string>
    <string name="host_or_ip">Host or IP :</string>
    <string name="enter_username">Enter username</string>
    <string name="enter_port_number">Enter port number</string>
    <string name="enter_ip_or_hostname">Enter IP or hostname</string>
    <string name="setup_new_router">SETUP NEW ROUTER</string>
    <string name="works_only_after_new_router_setup">*Works only after new router setup. If you already setup your router, it is not necessary to repeat.</string>
    <string name="set_connection_speed">SET SPEED LIMITS</string>
    <string name="in_premium_version">*IN PREMIUM VERSION :</string>
    <string name="how_many_ethernet_ports">SELECT QUANTITY OF ETHERNET PORTS IN YOUR ROUTER</string>
    <string name="attention">Please make sure that you connected to the router with default settings. After clicking \"I AGREE\" the app will divide ethernet ports of your router (from ETH2) to separate networks. Configuration will be possible only over WiFi. After closing the application by itself, reconnect to WiFi with password \"itremedy\", open the app again enter \"itremedy.online\" in the password field and press \"CONNECT\" button. After that you could set the connection speed on ports of the router. </string>
    <string name="wait">DON\'T TOUCH ANYTHING!\n Wait until the app is closed (usually about 30 seconds) then reconnect to WiFi with password \"itremedy\" (without quotes), start the app, enter password \"itremedy.online\" (without quotes) and connect, using button CONNECT, to your router. Print it in the Password field. IP, Port and username will stay the same. After that you could set the connection speed on ports of the router.</string>
    <string name="guest_wi_fi_setup">GUEST Wi-Fi SETUP</string>
    <string name="wi_fi_configuration">Wi-Fi CONFIGURATION</string>
    <string name="change_admin_password">CHANGE ADMIN\'S PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="quit">QUIT</string>
    <string name="set">SET</string>
    <string name="select_ports">Select Port</string>
    <string name="enter_new_speed">Enter Speed Limit</string>
    <string name="_0_unlimited">999=unlimited</string>
    <string name="please_wait">PLEASE WAIT</string>
    <string name="login">This application is intended for controlling MikroTik routers. Using it you can control speed limits of the ethernet ports of the router. Users of different ports will not have the opportunity to connect to each other. \n\t If you\'ve got new router turn it on, put the internet cable to the first port and connect to WiFi network that was created. Usually it calls\t "MikroTik-*****".\t If you also have\t "MikroTik-****A"\t don\'t use it this time or you would have no WiFi security.\n\t If you\'ve got Mikrotik router with any custom configuration, don\'t forget to back it up then do factory reset and setup it as new.\n\t We are not responsible for any harm that was done by using this application.</string>
    <string name="header_attention">ATTENTION!</string>
    <string name="i_agree">I AGREE</string>
    <string name="improvider">ImProvider</string>
    <string name="help"><font size="34">\t If you want to setup new router press button SETUP NEW ROUTER. \n\t If you want to connect router after setup enter password [itremedy.online] and press button CONNECT.</font></string>
    <string name="need_help">Need Help?</string>
    <string name="default_password">itremedy.online</string>
    <string name="_192_168_88_1">192.168.88.1</string>
    <string name="_22">22</string>
    <string name="admin">admin</string>
</resources>